‎那么…昨晚怎么样？
So… how was last night?
‎你跟男朋友分手了吗？
Did you break up with your boyfriend?
‎你难道不是很想知道吗？
Aren't you just dying to know?
‎想得抓心挠肝
Oh, I'm on pins and needles.
‎他带我去了一间高级餐厅
‎坐在桌边点菜那种
Well, he took me
to one of those fancy places
‎他带我去了一间高级餐厅
‎坐在桌边点菜那种
where you order at the table.
‎哇
Wow!
‎他可真把你宠坏了
He spoils you.
‎反正他吃得起
Well, he can afford it.
‎不知道我说没说过
‎他还是当地的名人
I don't know if I mentioned this,
but he's kind of a local celebrity.
‎他是风暴加里吗？
Is it Gary Storm?
‎新闻二台播天气预报那个人？
‎我超爱他的领结
The weather guy on Channel 2 news?
I love his bow ties.
‎风暴加里死于龙卷风了
Gary Storm died in a tornado.
‎你说的是雷电强尼
You're thinking of Johnny Thunder.
‎我的天！你在跟雷电强尼约会？
Oh my God! You're dating Johnny Thunder?
‎不是 我男友不是气象播报员
No, no. My guy's not a weatherman.
‎他开了好多间美发沙龙
‎你可能见过他的广告
He's got a bunch of salons.
You may have seen his commercials.
‎（爱心糖果）
‎发型在哪里？
Where's the hair?
‎发型在这里
There's the hair.
‎发型在哪里？
Where's the hair?
‎发型在这里
There's the hair.
‎爆炸
Explosion.
‎（菲丝轩）
‎菲丝轩 每天都有好发型
Chez Fez, where every day
is a good hair day.
‎我说 回见您呐
I said, good day.
‎你在跟菲丝约会？
You're dating Fez?
‎你认识菲丝？
You know Fez?
‎老交情了
Oh, we know Fez.
‎一 二 三 四…
-One, two, three, four!
‎在街上闲逛
‎和上周没什么两样
‎没什么事好做 就跟你唠唠嗑
‎这样挺好 这样挺好
‎（90年代秀）
‎你好 威斯康辛！
Hello, Wisconsin!
‎他俩知道你们在这里吗？
Do they know you guys are here?
‎他们才不管
Oh, they don't care.
‎腻歪得正上头呢
They're in the zone.
‎谁也拦不住
Nothing breaks it.
‎看好了
Watch this.
‎她怎么能亲我哥？
‎他的牙医检查到一半都崩溃了
How can she kiss my brother?
His dentist quit in the middle of an exam.
‎伙计们
Guys.
‎我离得太近 被粘住了
I got too close, and now I'm stuck in it.
‎大家都经历过
We've all been there.
‎亲热的时候
When you're in the middle of
a make out session,
‎你沉迷其中
and you're in the moment.
‎两个人双唇交融
And your lips just melt together.
‎他的舌头探到你的喉咙深处
And his tongue hits the hangy thing
in the back of your throat
‎感觉超好
and it feels so good.
‎什么？
What?
‎呃…舌头
The… uvula.
‎“优”点
The U-spot?
‎莉亚 你接过吻吗？
Leia, have you ever kissed anyone?
‎没有 一次都没有
Never. Not once.
‎从来没有发生过 好吗？
It's just never happened, okay?
‎六年级的时候
‎我比所有男孩都高30公分
In sixth grade, I was a foot taller
than all the other boys.
‎等他们能够着我嘴唇了
‎我却戴了两年进阶牙箍
And just when they got up to mouth level,
I did two years of advanced braces.
‎矫正器那种？
Like headgear?
‎比那还惨
It was so much worse.
‎上面有曲柄 我爸妈每晚都得拧一拧
There was a crank
my parents had to tighten every night.
‎感觉就像老爷车打火
It was like starting an old-timey car.
‎那也值了
Well, it was worth it.
‎你的笑容可美
You have such a beautiful smile.
‎你撩妹全年无休哇？
Do you ever take a day off?
‎我也想亲吻一个人
I wanna kiss someone.
‎我经常在想
I think about it all the time.
‎那是什么感觉？
What's it like?
‎好吧 这是紧急情况
Okay. This is an emergency.
‎我们得让你体验初吻
We need to get you your first kiss.
‎咱们去商场 迅速搞定
Let's go to the mall and knock this out.
‎商场？别让我对服装模特下手
The mall?
Oh, don't make me start on a mannequin.
‎太丢脸了
That's so embarrassing!
‎不是 那里到处都是男生
No. It's full of guys.
‎找个傻小子聊两句
‎给他秀下你的牙 然后啃上去
We'll find some goober, chat him up,
show him your teeth, lay one on him.
‎我不想把初吻给一个傻小子
I don't want my first kiss
to be with a goober.
‎你说得对
You're right.
‎我们应该等你足够自信
We should just wait until
you're confident enough,
‎情绪上做好准备
‎对自己足够有安全感…
emotionally ready, secure in who you are--
‎好吧 去商场
Okay, okay! Mall.
‎咱俩献出初吻的夏天 是吧 奥兹？
Summer of our first kiss. Right, Ozzie?
‎别把我和你相提并论 处女嘴
Don't lump me in with you,
you mouth virgin.
‎我有艾蒂安
I have Etienne.
‎兄弟 我想撑你
‎但你别继续胡编你的加拿大男友了
Bro, I wanna support you, but you gotta
stop with the fake Canadian boyfriend.
‎他超级真实的
Oh, he's real as hell.
‎我爸妈带我去蒙特利尔
‎看《歌剧魅影》
My parents took me
to see Phantom of the Opera in Montreal.
‎我遇到了可爱到不行的…艾蒂安
And I met the cutest guy… Etienne.
‎我们都伸手拿最后一件
‎加大号儿童纪念汗衫
We were both reaching for
the last kids' XL souvenir sweatshirt.
‎-他让给我了
‎-我们都没见过那衣裳
And he let me keep it.
‎-他让给我了
‎-我们都没见过那衣裳
We've never seen the sweatshirt.
‎随便啦 浪漫爱情朝你脸上泼酸
Whatever. You wouldn't know romance
if it threw acid in your face,
‎逼你独居谱写夜的乐章 你也不知道
forcing you into a life of solitude,
composing the music of the night.
‎天啊 我希望他是真的
God, I hope he's real.
‎你们什么时候来的？
When did you guys get here?
‎我俩亲热来着
We were making out.
‎菲丝是艾瑞克的朋友
Fez was one of Eric's friends.
‎一开始是来交换的学生
He started out
as a foreign exchange student, but…
‎可是…好像他们忘记把他换回去了
then I guess someone forgot
to exchange him back.
‎他是哪里人？
Where is he from?
‎我听说那地方可好了
I hear it's just lovely there.
‎你告诉他 你不想再见到他时
‎他跟你说了什么？
So, what did he say when you told him
you didn't wanna see him anymore?
‎我都没到那一步
I didn't get that far.
‎我是说 我试过了
I mean, I tried.
‎我跟他说我们完了 而他却说…
I told him it was over, and he said…
‎玩上位 玩下位 我无所谓
Over, under. I don't care.
‎我柔韧性好 宝贝
I'm flexible, baby.
‎于是我说：“我在努力专注于自己”
So I said,
"I'm trying to focus on myself."
‎我理解
I understand!
‎我想看着你专注于自己
And I'd like to watch you.
Watch you focus on yourself.
‎然后我说：“我们应该
‎像大人一样 好好谈谈”
And then I said, "We gotta
act like adults here. We gotta talk."
‎我做不到
I can't.
‎我嘴里有东西
My mouth is full.
‎把我的美甲嘬掉两片
He sucked off two of my Lee Press Ons.
‎好吧…
Well…
‎他口条挺结实 好得很
He's got a strong tongue. That's fine.
‎不 他真的很好 很显然他喜欢你
No. He really is a lovely guy,
and he obviously likes you.
‎要不就交往看看
Maybe see where it goes.
‎凯蒂 我真的用心听取你给我的建议
Kitty, I really took
all that advice you gave me to heart.
‎我不能总是游走于男人之间
‎我要花点时间 专注于自己
I need to stop jumping from guy to guy
and focus on myself for a while.
‎讨厌 这建议真心不赖
Darn it. That was good advice.
‎我不知道该怎么办 通常跟男人分手
I don't know what to do.
Normally, when I break up with a guy,
‎我只需要让假释官给他验个尿
I just tell the parole officer
to check his pee,
‎剩下的事就不用我操心了
and it takes care of itself, you know?
‎要不我去找他谈谈？也许打击能小点
Why don't I go talk to him?
Maybe I can let him down easy.
‎太好了 因为如果我去说
‎我肯定又会跟他上床
Oh good. 'Cause if I do it,
I'm definitely gonna sleep with him again.
‎干嘛？我在努力关注我自己
What? I was trying to focus on myself,
‎昨晚 我自己想跟他嘿咻 所以…
and last night myself wanted
to have sex with that guy, so…
‎欢迎再次光临“菲丝轩”
Welcome back to Chez Fez.
‎您在这里做发型 我们感觉真荣幸
It's always an honor
to have your hair in my chair.
‎我喜欢来这里
Well, I love coming here.
‎你过得这么好 我看了真高兴
I'm always so happy
to see how well you're doing.
‎爱心糖果免费吃 你是钱做的吗？
I mean, free Tootsie Rolls.
Are you made of money?
‎就是 你能相信吗？
Yes. Can you believe it?
‎跟你说 凯蒂女士 我喜欢这种生活
I tell you, Ms. Kitty. I love my life.
‎生意兴隆 我还有超模的水蛇腰
My business is booming.
I have the waist of Linda Evangelista.
‎而且如你所知…我还有一个相好的
And, as you know,
I have taken a lover.
‎其实吧
Actually,
‎我正是想跟你聊聊雪莉
I wanted to talk to you about Sherri.
‎是啊 她超美 对吧？
Oh yeah. She's so beautiful, right?
‎又温暖又黏糊 就像鸡肉派
She's warm and gooey,
like a chicken pot pie.
‎好吧
Uh-huh.
‎-但…
‎-更别说她的屁股蛋
-But--
-Oh, and don't get me started on her butt.
‎简直就是世界第八和第九大奇迹
It's like the eighth
and ninth Wonder of the World.
‎凯蒂女士 我已经很久
‎没对女人这么动心了 上回还是…杰姬
Ms. Kitty, I haven't felt this way
about a woman since, uh…
-Jackie.
‎对哈
Yes!
‎你们俩到底怎么回事？
Whatever happened between you two?
‎凯蒂女士…
Oh, Ms. Kitty!
‎我们去了享乐主义度假村
We were at Hedonism Resort.
‎在牙买加
In Hamaica.
‎有天晚上 我逮到她…
And I caught her on the phone one night…
‎跟麦克尔通电话
…with Michael.
‎凯尔索？
Kelso?
‎杜卡基斯
Dukakis.
‎当然是凯尔索！
Yes, of course Kelso!
‎她把我留在那里了
She left me there.
‎接下来的五天 我总是被踢出浴缸
And I spent the next five days
getting kicked out of hot tubs
‎人家嫌弃我话太多
for talking too much.
‎哦 亲爱的 我很遗憾
Oh, honey, I'm sorry.
‎但那是过去的事了
Oh, but that is the past.
‎而雪莉就是我的未来
And Sherri is my future.
‎要知道 凯蒂女士
You know, Ms. Kitty,
‎跟她在一起时…我已经不是男人了
when I'm with her… I'm no longer a man.
‎我就像是第一次看世界的小男孩
I'm like a little boy
seeing the world for the first time.
‎别误会 我拥有的
Don't get me wrong, I still have
‎是男人的声音…男人的翘臀
the voice of a man and the… hips of a man
‎还有…男人的嘴巴
and, uh… the mouth of a man.
‎搞得人神魂颠倒
It's very confusing.
‎可是 当我拥她在怀中…
But when I hold her in my arms…
‎哦 凯蒂女士
Oh, Ms. Kitty.
‎感觉就像世界融化了…
It's like the world just melts away…
‎只有我们两个
and there's only us,
‎直到永远
for eternity.
‎对不起 凯蒂女士 你刚才说什么？
I'm sorry, Ms. Kitty.
What were you saying?
‎我刚才说…
I was saying…
‎-我喜欢爱情！
‎-爱情！
-I love love!
-Oh!
‎永远别放手
Don't ever let her go!
‎谢谢你送我们 爷爷
Thanks for the ride, Grandpa.
‎啥时候想从我家出来
‎我都乐意开车送你们
Any time you kids wanna
get out of my house, I'll drive you.
‎应该不会太久
This shouldn't take too long.
‎你们需要什么吗？
You guys need anything?
‎一个奇迹
A miracle.
‎好吧
Fine.
‎我就待在这里看报纸
I'll be right over here, reading my paper.
‎你真有品味
You have great taste.
‎这是新款离子按摩椅
This is the new ionic massage chair.
‎-让我给你展示一些功能
‎-听着 我知道你只是在尽职责
-Let me show you some of the features.
-Look. I know you're just doing your job.
‎不过还是去那边吧
But go do it over there.
‎只要别在这里就行了
Any place that's not here.
‎就这么两下 你可别想把我赶走
You are gonna have to do
better than that to get rid of me.
‎它有多档速度 科林斯皮革
It's got variable speeds,
Corinthian leather,
‎你要是再笑一个 我再加送同日派送
and if you turn that frown upside-down,
I'll throw in same-day delivery.
‎我先同日把你的屁股
‎派送进那花盆里 看你…
I'm about to same-day deliver
your ass into that planter if you…
Oh…
‎乖乖
Sweet Lord.
‎这椅子长着指头呢
This chair's got fingers!
‎一张信用卡就能搞定
All I need is, like, a credit card.
‎赶紧的
Just make it happen.
‎我真的超紧张
‎后背的汗都流到屁股了
I'm really nervous.
‎我真的超紧张
‎后背的汗都流到屁股了
My back sweat's
being funneled right into my butt.
‎说明你的身体已经做好浪漫准备了
That's just your body
getting ready for romance.
‎你可爱 又聪明 超赞的 绝对能行
You're cute, you're smart,
and you're awesome. You can do this.
‎这就是香肠过节的节奏啊
It's a total sausage fest.
‎就是 这么多男的
Yeah, look at all these guys.
‎“山核桃农场”搞免费香肠试吃
No. Hickory Farms is giving out
free samples.
‎艾蒂安喜欢烟熏高达奶酪
Etienne loves a nice smoked Gouda.
‎-好吧 如果真有这个人 那他姓啥？
‎-圣伯纳德
-Fine. If he's real, what's his last name?
-St. Bernard.
‎-在哪上学？
‎-圣伯纳德
-What school?
-St. Bernard's.
‎-他有宠物吗？
‎-卷毛比雄
-Does he have any pets?
-Bichon Frisé.
‎等等 倒是提醒我了
Wait. That reminds me.
‎我给一只狗做过心肺复苏术
‎那算是亲亲吗？
I've given CPR to a dog.
Does that count as a kiss?
‎去吧 你能行
-Go. You got this!
‎我要两勺 你
I'd like two scoops. Of you.
‎对不起
I'm sorry.
‎嘿 性感帅哥 你在吃葡萄吗？
Hey, sexy. You eatin' grapes?
‎对 因为他才九岁
Yeah, because he's nine.
‎对不起 我爸爸有一件同款的上衣
I'm so sorry. My dad has that shirt!
‎女士 你不能进柜台后
Ma'am, you are not allowed
behind the counter.
‎我已经不在乎了 放下勺子 咱俩走着
I don't care anymore.
Now put down the scooper,
and let's do this.
‎没必要搞这么复杂吧
You don't have to make this so difficult!
‎跑了
Got away.
‎-好了
‎-你们赶紧走
-Okay!
-You kids need to leave.
‎你有没有我这个年纪的儿子？
You don't happen
to have a son my age, do you?
‎一切顺利？
So it went well?
‎才怪 走吧 格温在哪里？
No. Let's go. Where's Gwen?
‎格温 走啦
Gwen, let's bounce.
‎格温
Gwen!
‎再见 凯文 刚才很开心
Bye, Kevin. That was fun.
‎我这辈子最爽的一天
Best day of my life.
‎冷静 凯文
Calm down, Kevin.
‎好吧
Okay.
‎不是吧？
Seriously?
‎总得有人搞点甜头吧
One of us had to get some.
‎宝贝 你好像对我的唇膏过敏
Babe, I think you might be having
a reaction to one of my Lip Smackers.
‎真的吗？
Really?
‎我觉得没事
I feel fine.
‎嗯 瞅着没啥事
Yeah, it looks fine.
‎简直是一场灾难
‎我上了逐客名单 以后也去不了了
That was a disaster.
And I'm on a list now, so I can't go back.
‎-如果我需要新鞋怎么办？
‎-什么叫“如果”？
-What if I need new shoes?
-What do you mean, "what if"?
‎真恶心
Whoa, gross.
‎你的嘴怎么跟猴屁股似的？
Why does your mouth
look like a monkey's ass?
‎猴屁股？
A monkey's ass?
‎这是好话还是赖话？
Like, in a good or bad way?
‎还是带你去急诊室吧
Come on. We should probably
get you to the urgent care.
‎你不是说没事吗？
You said it wasn't bad.
‎那是我刚才坐得舒服 不想起来
I was just comfortable,
and I didn't wanna get up.
‎老天 我在商场寻找邂逅
Oh my God. I'm at the mall
throwing myself at randos.
‎他们俩却嘬蜜嘬到嘴肿
Meanwhile, they're making out so much,
his lips revolted.
‎我是怎么了？
What's wrong with me?
‎难道没人想舔我身价两千的牙齿吗？
Doesn't anyone want
to lick these $2,000 teeth?
‎好吧
Wow. Okay.
‎我倒有一个主意 之前不想说
Well, there is another idea,
but I didn't wanna bring it up
‎是因为有点诡异 外加慌不择路
because it feels
kinda weird and desperate.
‎这是现实
I think we're there.
‎你可以吻杰伊
You could kiss Jay.
‎他很帅 还总撩你
He's cute. He's always flirting with you.
‎而且 他还是凯尔索家的男人
Plus, he's a Kelso.
‎所以呢？什么意思？
So? What does that mean?
‎渣男一个
He's a man-whore.
Oh.
‎虽然很有诱惑力 但还是算了
As great as that sounds, I'm gonna pass.
‎再说了 他也是咱们的朋友
‎太尴尬了 肯定还有别人
Plus, he's our friend. It's too awkward.
There's gotta be someone else.
‎总归还有泳池里奇
There's always Town Pool Ricky.
‎好啊 救生员 多性感
Oh great, a lifeguard. That's hot.
‎没有 他就是来回晃悠一下
‎捞捞池子里的创可贴
No, he just hangs out
and collects the floating Band-Aids.
‎但他单身 乐意鬼混
But he's single and ready to mingle.
‎至少他衣服上这么写着
At least that's what his shirt says.
‎要不就杰伊吧？
So Jay?
‎就杰伊了
Jay, it is.
‎雷德 要我说 这按摩椅不靠谱
Red, I'm not sure
about this massage chair.
‎咱们说好的 不改陈设 以防以后眼瞎
We said we wouldn't change anything
in case one of us went blind.
‎对不住 美女
I'm sorry, gorgeous.
‎我最不愿意让你难过压力大了
The last thing I wanna do
is stress you out or upset you.
‎你没事吧？
Are you feeling okay?
‎可爽了
I'm awesome.
‎凯蒂 你可把菲丝的事办砸了
Kitty, you did a terrible job with Fez.
‎他说他爱我 你跟他说了什么？
He told me he loved me.
What did you say to him?
‎我年纪大了 说过什么记不太清
I… I'm an older lady.
I can't recall the exact words.
‎凯蒂 他说要共度人生 还哭了
Kitty. He talked about a life together.
He started crying.
‎然后还给他妈妈打电话 她也哭
Then he got his mom on the phone.
She started crying.
‎亲爱的
Honey.
‎雪莉来了
Sherri's here.
‎她肯定是来了 你好像在神游
I know she is. I'm not sure you are.
‎这俏皮话不赖 亲
Good one, babe.
‎对不起 我只是…当时有点被带跑了
I'm sorry. I just… I got…
I got swept up in the moment.
‎他那么贴心
He's so sweet.
‎他的语气就像
‎我看得不咋懂的言情小说
And his words sound like
a romance novel that I barely understand.
‎我该怎么办？这家伙简直甩不掉
What am I gonna do?
This guy is undumpable.
‎显然 我也做不来
Well, clearly, I can't hack it.
‎我们得找一个狠角色
We need someone who is just ruthless.
‎劈头盖脸
Who will go straight for the jugular.
‎一斧子要他命
An ax murderer.
‎雷德 亲爱的？
Red, honey?
‎咱们要不要养一只猫？
Should we get a cat?
‎暖烘烘放腿上
Just something warm to have right here,
‎陪着我爽
while I'm… chillin'.
‎椅子 我得找雷德的真身谈谈
Chair, I need to talk to the real Red.
‎该死 凯蒂
Damn it, Kitty!
‎你干嘛非得把电拔了？
Did you have to pull the plug?
‎所以我才不在医院的文件上写你名字
That's exactly why I don't put your name
on those papers at the hospital.
‎斧头杀手有了
There's our ax murderer.
‎你来啦
Hey, you.
‎其他人呢？我以为是先在这里集合
‎然后去打保龄球呢
Where is everyone? I thought
we're meeting up here before bowling.
‎保龄球馆关门 他们没球了
Oh, the bowling alley's closed.
They ran out of balls.
‎过来坐
Come sit.
‎好吧
Okay.
‎看看那片天空
Look at that sky.
‎星星很亮 月亮…也很亮
The stars are so bright, and the moon is
also bright.
‎这我倒没想过
I never thought of it like that.
‎有点浪漫 不是吗？
Kind of romantic, don't you think?
‎哇 这里可以
‎直接看到那老太太的浴缸
Whoa, you can see
right into that old lady's bathtub.
‎她在哭
Oh, she's crying.
‎她老公好像刚刚挂了
I think her husband just died.
‎-莉亚？
‎-嗯？
-Leia?
-Yeah?
‎我知道你的用意
I know what's going on here.
‎很好 稍等
Oh good. Gimme a sec.
‎好了 继续
Okay, I'm back.
‎莉亚
Leia.
‎我不会吻你的
I'm not going to kiss you.
‎什么？
What?
‎连你也这样？天啊 太丢脸了
Not even you?
Oh my God, this is so embarrassing.
‎我遁了
I'll be in here now.
‎不要 别觉得难为情
Hey, stop. Don't be embarrassed.
‎听着 我觉得你很棒
Look. I think you're great.
‎你可爱又聪明 还很风趣
You're cute and smart and interesting.
‎真的吗？
Really?
‎对
Yeah.
‎所以我们不该接吻
That's why I don't think we should kiss.
‎听着
Look.
‎莉亚 我不想毫无意义地调情
Leia, I just don't want to be
some meaningless hookup.
‎知道吗？
You know?
‎如果要发生的话
‎我希望发生得自然而然
Like, if it's gonna happen,
I want it to just happen.
‎发生得美妙
And I want it to be amazing.
‎你说得真好
Okay, that was really nice.
‎你确定不想接吻吗？
You sure you don't wanna kiss?
‎我后背狂冒汗 已经准备好浪漫了
Because my back sweat is
really telling me it's time for romance.
‎看看这个夏天会怎样发展吧
Let's just see where the summer takes us.
‎谁知道呢？
Who knows?
‎也许会变得很特别
It might be somewhere really special.
‎你好 雷德先生
Hello, Mr. Red.
Oh.
‎菲丝 你来了 很好
Fez, you're here. Good.
‎听着
Look.
‎这话我只能这么说
There's no easy way to say this.
‎完了
It's over.
‎不要啊
Oh no.
‎太糟糕了
That's terrible.
‎你还剩多少日子？
How long do you have left?
‎-什么？
‎-别担心 雷德先生
-What?
-Don't worry, Mr. Red.
‎你走了之后 我会照顾凯蒂女士
I'll take care of Ms. Kitty
when you're gone.
‎无微不至
In every possible way.
‎我说的是你和雪莉
I'm talking about you and Sherri.
‎你们俩结束了
The two of you are over.
‎什么？
What?
‎你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
‎这是在开玩笑吗？
Is this a joke?
‎-咚咚咚
‎-是谁？
-Knock, knock.
-Who's there?
‎雪莉把你甩了
Sherri's dumping you.
‎这可不好笑
That's not funny.
‎振作起来 孩子
Chin up, kid.
‎你尽力了
You gave it your best shot.
‎看着我
Look at me!
‎想伤我的心 就看着我的眼睛
Look me in the eyes
if you're going to rip my heart out!
‎对不起 雷德先生 我不该大吼大叫
Oh, I'm sorry, Mr. Red.
I shouldn't have raised my voice.
‎但我看到了我们俩的未来
But I saw a life for us.
‎假日 旅行 白头偕老
Holidays, travel, dying of an old age
‎临终也不忘做爱
‎拧得像双圈脆饼一样合葬
while making love so we could be
buried together like a pretzel.
‎认倒霉吧
Tough break.
‎是啊 真的很霉
Yeah. Really tough.
‎明明生活中其他方面都圆满了
Everything else in my life
has lined up perfectly.
‎但一起分享的那个最重要的人…
But the most important part,
someone to share it with…
‎却没有
it's missing.
‎孩子 是这样
Here's the thing, kid.
‎你很奇怪
You're weird.
‎但总有一天
‎你会找到喜好你这口的人
But, one day, you're gonna find
someone who loves that.
‎再说了 你真的准备好
‎照顾一个有孩子的女人吗？
Besides, were you really ready for
the responsibility of a woman with kids?
‎她有孩子？
She has kids?
‎一个四十多岁的女人
‎有孩子也不奇怪啊
It shouldn't be shocking
that a woman in her forties has kids.
‎她四十多岁了？
She's in her forties?!
‎哎呀！幸好躲过一劫
Whew!
Really dodged a bullet there.
‎真不敢相信 杰伊居然没吻你
I still can't believe Jay didn't kiss you.
‎奇怪 就算没有如我所愿
‎我也一点也不担心
It's so weird. Even though things didn't
turn out like I wanted, I'm not worried.
‎我有点期待之后的进展 你懂吗？
Kind of excited for what's next, you know?
‎太懂了
I so do.
‎我觉得自己简直换了一个人
I just feel like a brand-new woman.
‎迫不及待想体验未来的人生了…
I can't wait to see
what's on the horizon for me--
‎妈 谢谢你送我们
‎但你能去别处找青春吗？
Mom. Thanks for the ride, but could you
go get your groove back somewhere else?
‎好 我要找家“现代休闲”买衣裳去
Okay, okay. I'll go find myself
at Contempo Casual.
‎那你打算怎么办？等着杰伊行动吗？
So what's the plan?
Just wait around for Jay?
‎如果他想让我等他
If he wanted me to wait for around him,
‎就不该告诉我
‎我有多可爱、聪明和风趣
he shouldn't have told me
how cute and smart and interesting I am.
‎你个傻瓜
You dork.
‎我一直都在说你有多棒
I've been telling you all along
how awesome you are,
‎有个男孩说了 你才明白？
but it took some guy to say it
for it all to sink in.
‎没有
No.
‎嗯 是这样
Yeah, that's what happened.
‎随便啦 我喜欢这个崭新自信的莉亚
Whatever. I like the new confident Leia.
‎我也是
Me too.
‎话说 我马上回来
Actually, I'll be right back.
‎早安 艾蒂安
Bonjour, Etienne.
‎（歌剧魅影）
‎我也想你
I miss you too.
‎什么叫你的朋友觉得我不存在？
What do you mean
your friends don't think I'm real?
‎跟这些左派美国佬一个德性
It's the same thing
with these gauche Americans.
‎是啊
Yes, yes, yes, yes. Yes.
‎对
Yes.
‎字幕翻译：Zeo Niu